Adlet Zhantassov

+7 777 700 3300 | adlet.zh19966@gmail.com | Astana, Kazakhstan

Summary

iOS application developer with 9 months experience learning building interactive and stable applications. Has 3 year experience in SAP ABAP development and SAP/Non-SAP integration tools. Has experience developing RPA projects using Python libraries and UiPath.

Experience

Yandex mobile school | Moscow iOS developer | 06/2023 - Present

everything related to iOS apps development

TOO BTS | Astana, Kazakhstan

SAP PI/PO developer | 05/2022 - Present

Responsible for delivery of integrations of SAP/Non-SAP applications, middleware architecture.

Delivery of SAP PI/PO integrations/solutions for ongoing projects and Change requests using different means of connections: REST, microservices, JDBC, BPM, iDoc, SOAP, others.

Delivery of integrations/solutions for ongoing projects and Change requests in SAP ERP using ABAP programming.

STARTIOS | Astana, Kazakhstan

iOS developer courses | 12/2022 - Present

My stack: Swift, Git, Snapkit, UiKit, Concurrency and Multithreading, Urlsession, Alamofire, CoreData, Firebase, User defaults, Design Patterns, MVC, MVP+R, MVVM+C, Clean Swift, Viper, Notifications, Unit Testing

https://github.com/Adletski

KMG-Kumkol | Astana, Kazakhstan SAP ABAP developer | 11/2020 - 03/2023

Knowledge of OO ABAP, Web Dynpro, Web-services, RFC, Adobe Forms, User-Exits, BAdI, Enhancements, ALV, BDC, BAPI, LSMW, Open SQL, ALE/EDI.

Experience in code optimization, knowledge of performance analysis tools.

Experience with SAP ABAP design and development.

Flyingbird LTD | Astana, Kazakhstan

RPA Python developer | 02/2022 - 09/2022

Developing Robotic process automation projects using Python libraries and UiPath.

Skills

ABAP, SAP PI/PO, Python, UiPath, Swift

Education

ECUST I Shanghai, China

Oil-gas Storage and Transportation Automation Engineering | 06/2020

1st lyceum school | Astana, Kazakhstan 05/2014

Red diploma